Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student Records, 1998 -- 2018; UA235.001; 74.4 Linear Feet
  - Alyousef, Wed, 2016-05 -- 2017-07; UA235.001.098.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 44)
  - Abdulmajeed, Afnan, 2016-06; UA235.001.098.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 45)
  - Alshuhail, Ola A., 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 46)
  - Alzayer, Ahmad A., 2015-06 -- 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 47)
  - Alzayer, Ahmad A., 2015-06 -- 2016-05; UA235.001.098.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 48)
  - Amin, Sarah A., 2016-07; UA235.001.098.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Amin, Sarah A., 2016-07; UA235.001.098.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 50)
  - Asali, Ammar, 2016-09; UA235.001.098.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 51)
  - Asali, Ammar, 2013-07 -- 2015-06; UA235.001.098.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 98, Folder 52)
  - Abdul-Aziz, Sama E., 2018; UA235.005100; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Adeloye, Oluwapelumi A., 2018; UA235.005101; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Ali, Omar A., 2018; UA235.005102; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Anand, Alisha A., 2018; UA235.005103; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Anderson, Chad, 2018; UA235.005104; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Anekwe, Gloria, 2018; UA235.005105; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Baftechi, Fatemeh, 2018; UA235.005106; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Barbera, Kelly Ann, 2018; UA235.005107; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Batlle, Jonathan W., 2018; UA235.005108; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Batra, Monisha, 2018; UA235.005109; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Berglund, Jason, 2018; UA235.005110; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Bernet, Isamary, 2018; UA235.005111; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Betances, Elizabeth, 2018; UA235.005112; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Bhardwaj, Saloni, 2018; UA235.005113; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Bosco, Isaac J., 2018; UA235.005114; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Boucher, Steven W., 2018; UA235.005115; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Britton, Maritza S., 2018; UA235.005116; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Calandrelli, Gian R., 2018; UA235.005117; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Camacho, Yusleisy, 2018; UA235.005118; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Campbell, Kevin W., 2018; UA235.005119; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Cardaropoli Jr., David M., 2018; UA235.005120; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Cassella, Camille G., 2018; UA235.005121; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Cerulli, Shelby L., 2018; UA235.005122; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Cheng, Austin, 2018; UA235.005123; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Chiu, Eva, 2018; UA235.005124; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Choe, Leandro M., 2018; UA235.005125; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - Choi, Patrick, 2018; UA235.005126; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Chugh, Sonia, 2018; UA235.005127; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Chung, Na Eun, 2018; UA235.005128; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Coletti, Matthew E., 2018; UA235.005129; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Collins, Brian A., 2018; UA235.005130; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Collins, Christine C., 2018; UA235.005131; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - Cook, Hannah C., 2018; UA235.005132; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - Coppola, Kyle A., 2018; UA235.005133; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - Cronk, Stephen M., 2018; UA235.005134; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - Cunningham, Laura A., 2018; UA235.005135; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - Darmetko, Taylor R., 2018; UA235.005136; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 37)
  - Dobbins, Joshua C., 2018; UA235.005137; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 38)
  - Donovan, Kaitlin T., 2018; UA235.005138; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 39)
  - D'Silva, Sharon L., 2018; UA235.005139; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 40)
  - Ebrahimi, Nahrin, 2018; UA235.005140; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 41)
  - Eidelman, Alec S., 2018; UA235.005141; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 42)
  - Elmaleh, Elizabeth, 2018; UA235.005142; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 43)
  - Elpers, Amanda M., 2018; UA235.005143; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 44)
  - Fadie, Holly L., 2018; UA235.005144; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 45)
  - Finberg, Abbe, 2018; UA235.005145; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 46)
  - Flaherty, Nicholas M., 2018; UA235.005146; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 47)
  - Fraga, Salome, 2018; UA235.005147; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 48)
  - Ganley, Brian P., 2018; UA235.005148; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 49)
  - Gaudet, Sunny T., 2018; UA235.005149; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 50)
  - Geary, Robert E., 2018; UA235.005150; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 51)
  - Gerkowicz, Lauren A., 2018; UA235.005151; 1 Folder(s) (Box 99, Folder 52)
  - Ghanta, Ranjit, 2018; UA235.005152; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Gillani, Sareena, 2018; UA235.005153; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Giron, Oliver J., 2018; UA235.005154; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Golub, Michael J., 2018; UA235.005155; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Gomes, Alexander, 2018; UA235.005156; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Grosser,Levi Y., 2018; UA235.005157; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Guerra, Beatriz, 2018; UA235.005158; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Hamidi, Gyve L., 2018; UA235.005159; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Han, Daniel J., 2018; UA235.005160; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Hanger, Samuel P., 2018; UA235.005161; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Hayes, Amanda E., 2018; UA235.005162; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Herrero, Krysten M., 2018; UA235.005163; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Hirschfeld, Joelle S., 2018; UA235.005164; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Hong, Hyeduk, 2018; UA235.005165; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Hong, Isaac E., 2018; UA235.005166; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Hornung, Craig P., 2018; UA235.005167; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Huang, Shou Chia, 2018; UA235.005168; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Huynh, Patrick T., 2018; UA235.005169; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Irving, Jetoria L., 2018; UA235.005170; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Johnson III, Robert E., 2018; UA235.005171; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Johnston, Chelsea N., 2018; UA235.005172; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Jonna, Kyle R., 2018; UA235.005173; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Joseph, Sonya, 2018; UA235.005174; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Kaliher, Joshua M., 2018; UA235.005175; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Kao, Pei-Yun, 2018; UA235.005176; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Katz, Carli S., 2018; UA235.005177; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Keezel, Mary L., 2018; UA235.005178; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Samuel R., 2018; UA235.005179; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Khemka, Amrita, 2018; UA235.005180; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Kim, Benjamin Y., 2018; UA235.005181; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Kim, Christina M., 2018; UA235.005182; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - Kim, Elizabeth J., 2018; UA235.005183; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 32)
  - Kim, Timothy J., 2018; UA235.005184; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 33)
  - Kirsch, David P., 2018; UA235.005185; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 34)
  - Kotchinian, Haroutioun A., 2018; UA235.005186; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - Kounsalieh, John S., 2018; UA235.005187; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 36)
  - Kozlowski, Elizabeth R., 2018; UA235.005188; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 37)
  - Krass, David W., 2018; UA235.005189; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 38)
  - Krost, Daniel M., 2018; UA235.005190; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 39)
  - Lai, Albert, 2018; UA235.005191; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 40)
  - Lalonde, Aaron, 2018; UA235.005192; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 41)
  - Le, Annie, 2018; UA235.005193; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 42)
  - Leahey, Hannah M., 2018; UA235.005194; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 43)
  - Lee, Ji Youn, 2018; UA235.005195; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 44)
  - Lee, Soo Jin, 2018; UA235.005196; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 45)
  - Levesque, Lena, 2018; UA235.005197; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 46)
  - Lor, Sandy, 2018; UA235.005198; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 47)
  - Manter, Benjamin W., 2018; UA235.005199; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 48)
  - Martin, Carly S., 2018; UA235.005200; 1 Folder(s) (Box 100, Folder 49)
  - Meyers, Kimberly A., 2018; UA235.005201; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Michael, Veronica, 2018; UA235.005202; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Milder, Megan J., 2018; UA235.005203; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Monfette, Gregory W., 2018; UA235.005204; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Monshizadegan, Christopher O., 2018; UA235.005205; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Murali, Sangita, 2018; UA235.005206; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Muro, Erin E., 2018; UA235.005207; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Murray, Kirk W., 2018; UA235.005208; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Myung, Mijung, 2018; UA235.005209; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Myung, Mijung, 2018; UA235.005210; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Nahm, Byung Min, 2018; UA235.005211; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Naski, Alexandra C., 2018; UA235.005212; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Ngo, Tiffany D. T., 2018; UA235.005213; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Nguyen, Mindy V., 2018; UA235.005214; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Nguyen, Tuyen Thanh, 2018; UA235.005215; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Nice, Spencer L., 2018; UA235.005216; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Noorian, Pasha A., 2018; UA235.005217; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Novoa, Jose A., 2018; UA235.005218; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Ghattas, Monica, 2018; UA235.005219; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Moini, Micheline, 2018; UA235.005220; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - d'Angelo, Nika, 2018; UA235.005221; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Chauhan, Vikram, 2018; UA235.005222; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Khan, Abdul Jabbar, 2018; UA235.005223; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Khan, Abdul Jabbar, 2014 -- 2015; UA235.005224; 2 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 24-25)
  - Oh, Jae S., 2018; UA235.005225; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - Ortiz, Leigh Ann Klein, 2018; UA235.005226; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - Owen, Joseph N., 2018; UA235.005227; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - Park, Jihee, 2018; UA235.005228; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - Park, Linda, 2018; UA235.005229; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 30)
  - Patel, Aekta A., 2018; UA235.005230; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 31)
  - Patel, Dhruva, 2018; UA235.005231; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 32)
  - Patel, Priyanka A., 2018; UA235.005232; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 33)
  - Patel, Sejal S., 2018; UA235.005233; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 34)
  - Peacock-Villada, Alexandra Y., 2018; UA235.005234; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 35)
  - Peng, Cong, 2018; UA235.005235; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 36)
  - Petty, Allison G., 2018; UA235.005236; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 37)
  - Phan, Belinda H., 2018; UA235.005237; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 38)
  - Phan, Tuvy L., 2018; UA235.005238; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 39)
  - Phen, Nathaniel C., 2018; UA235.005239; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 40)
  - Powers, Alyssha, 2018; UA235.005240; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 41)
  - Powers, Meghan, 2018; UA235.005241; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 42)
  - Quest, Melanie A., 2018; UA235.005242; 1 Folder(s) (Box 101, Folder 43)
  - Rathore, Sobia, 2018; UA235.005243; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Redden, Tracy M., 2018; UA235.005244; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Rehman, Fazalur, 2018; UA235.005245; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Reichheld, Timothy L., 2018; UA235.005246; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Reimers, Nathaniel O., 2018; UA235.005247; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Rhodes, Anson L., 2018; UA235.005248; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Roberts, Stevie, 2018; UA235.005249; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Sacks, Hayley R., 2018; UA235.005250; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Salvani, Joemari S., 2018; UA235.005251; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Sauve, Jeremie E., 2018; UA235.005252; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Seay, Daniel J., 2018; UA235.005253; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Shareef, Fatima, 2018; UA235.005254; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Sheikh, Yusuf A., 2018; UA235.005255; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Shrestha, Avigya, 2018; UA235.005256; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Sico, Madison E., 2018; UA235.005257; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Siegel, Jordan R., 2018; UA235.005258; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Son, Heejeong, 2018; UA235.005259; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Spencer, Cody, 2018; UA235.005260; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Stang, Meghan E., 2018; UA235.005261; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Surti, Gopi, 2018; UA235.005262; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Tarpy, Alyssa M., 2018; UA235.005263; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 21)
  - Taylor, Andrew T., 2018; UA235.005264; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Tchintchin, Tracy A., 2018; UA235.005265; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Tengco, Derrick G., 2018; UA235.005266; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - Trager, Lauren R., 2018; UA235.005267; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - Vaillancourt, Nicholas A., 2018; UA235.005268; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Vega, Mikenah J., 2018; UA235.005269; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Vu, Cuong, 2018; UA235.005270; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - Vu, Eric P., 2018; UA235.005271; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - Walker, Shayla M., 2018; UA235.005272; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Wang, Jing, 2018; UA235.005273; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - Wang, Joanna Y., 2018; UA235.005274; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Ward, Raven M., 2018; UA235.005275; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Ward, Samantha M., 2018; UA235.005276; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - Werner III, Harry N., 2018; UA235.005277; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - Whitmer, Thomas, 2018; UA235.005278; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Williams, Lauren B., 2018; UA235.005279; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 37)
  - Wirth, Jared M., 2018; UA235.005280; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 38)
  - Wong, Brandon C., 2018; UA235.005281; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 39)
  - Wong, Lawrence C., 2018; UA235.005282; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 40)
  - Wong, Monita C., 2018; UA235.005283; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 41)
  - Woo, Sung M., 2018; UA235.005284; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 42)
  - Wood, Christina L., 2018; UA235.005285; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 43)
  - Wu, Alan, 2018; UA235.005286; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 44)
  - Wu Jr., Christopher T., 2018; UA235.005287; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 45)
  - Wyman, Trista D., 2018; UA235.005288; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 46)
  - Yasin, Areeb, 2018; UA235.005289; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 47)
  - Yazbak, Abigail C., 2018; UA235.005290; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 48)
  - Yi, Chaeryun, 2018; UA235.005291; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 49)
  - Yim, Joanna Y., 2018; UA235.005292; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 50)
  - Yu, Adam R., 2018; UA235.005293; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 51)
  - Zhao, Lei, 2018; UA235.005294; 1 Folder(s) (Box 102, Folder 52)
  - Asghar, Syed, 2018; UA235.005295; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Brar, Poonampreet Kaur, 2018; UA235.005296; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Hadadi, Elaf, 2018; UA235.005297; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Khan, Moiz, 2018; UA235.005298; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - La Salvia, Joan, 2018; UA235.005299; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Norbhu, Kesang, 2018; UA235.005300; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Patel, Pinak, 2018; UA235.005301; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Seith, Ana, 2018; UA235.005302; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Shah, Ashna, 2018; UA235.005303; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Shen, Shiqian, 2018; UA235.005304; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Verma, Japneet, 2018; UA235.005305; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Wilson, Dalia, 2018; UA235.005306; 1 Folder(s) (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Post Graduate files, 1948 -- 2018; UA235.002; 42.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains Post-Graduate student files. Types of records found within student files include transcripts of Dental School and undergraduate institutions, admission letters and recommendations, applications, evaluations, photographs, and other personal information. The year listed for each student is the date of their graduation.
  This series is arranged as found.
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Al-Fulaji, Waleed, 2004; UA235.002.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Almazyed, Kamelah M, 1998; UA235.002.041.00002 (Box 41)
  - Abbasy, Jamil, 2006; UA235.002.041.00003 (Box 41)
  - Al-Ghafli, Suhail, 2006; UA235.002.041.00004 (Box 41)
  - Abu Al-Saud, Haythem, 2001; UA235.002.041.00005 (Box 41)
  - Avery-Miranda, Lauren, 2006; UA235.002.041.00006 (Box 41)
  - Balla, Amalia, 2005; UA235.002.041.00007 (Box 41)
  - Beagan, Bryan F, 2005; UA235.002.041.00008 (Box 41)
  - Blandon, Guillermina, 2004; UA235.002.041.00009 (Box 41)
  - Busciglic, Derek M, 2005; UA235.002.041.00010 (Box 41)
  - Cole, Shannon E, 2005; UA235.002.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - Dawson, Tavia N, 2005; UA235.002.041.00012 (Box 41)
  - Engler-Hamm, Daniel, 2003; UA235.002.041.00013 (Box 41)
  - Evelyn, Kelsey, 2005; UA235.002.041.00014 (Box 41)
  - Forbes, Rachel L, 2005; UA235.002.041.00015 (Box 41)
  - Hate, Sameer N, 2003; UA235.002.041.00016 (Box 41)
  - Hoang, Tuan, 2005; UA235.002.041.00017 (Box 41)
  - Huang, Liang-Gie, 2006; UA235.002.041.00018 (Box 41)
  - Jaw, Shiow-Jiin, 2004; UA235.002.041.00019 (Box 41)
  - Jellock, Elizabeth, 2004; UA235.002.041.00020 (Box 41)
  - Karapanou, Virginia, 1999; UA235.002.041.00021 (Box 41)
  - Khanbodaghi, Azita, 2006; UA235.002.041.00022 (Box 41)
  - Mohammadi Araghi, Shadi, 2004; UA235.002.041.00023 (Box 41)
  - Nart, Jose, 2004; UA235.002.041.00024 (Box 41)
  - Olszewski, Teddi, 2006; UA235.002.041.00025 (Box 41)
  - Ortiz, Javier, 2006; UA235.002.041.00026 (Box 41)
  - Resnick, Anthea S, 2005; UA235.002.041.00027 (Box 41)
  - Stanley, Dwight P, 2005; UA235.002.041.00028 (Box 41)
  - Stiefel, Daniel B, 2004; UA235.002.041.00029 (Box 41)
  - Togias, Kris T, 2005; UA235.002.041.00030 (Box 41)
  - Tran, Linda L, 1997; UA235.002.041.00031 (Box 41)
  - Wells, Brian T, 2005; UA235.002.041.00032 (Box 41)
  - Sabnani, Romney, 2005; UA235.002.041.00033 (Box 41)
  - Seibel, Kristine, 2004; UA235.002.041.00034 (Box 41)
  - Alyassi, Monaf A, 2006; UA235.002.041.00035 (Box 41)
  - Attar, Moaz H, 2005; UA235.002.041.00036 (Box 41)
  - Chartzoulakis, Maria, 2005; UA235.002.041.00037 (Box 41)
  - Chen, Katrina, 2004; UA235.002.041.00038 (Box 41)
  - Cho, Hyunki, 2000; UA235.002.041.00039 (Box 41)
  - Clark, Meghan, 2006; UA235.002.041.00040 (Box 41)
  - Currie, Peter, 2005; UA235.002.041.00041 (Box 41)
  - Cwiklinski, Michael T, 2005; UA235.002.041.00042 (Box 41)
  - DiMarzio, Michael P, 2006; UA235.002.041.00043 (Box 41)
  - Dodson, Zachary, 2006; UA235.002.041.00044 (Box 41)
  - Drakos, Dimitrios, 2002; UA235.002.041.00045 (Box 41)
  - El-Ghadi, Moftah, 2005; UA235.002.041.00046 (Box 41)
  - Fraulini, Niho, 2005; UA235.002.041.00047 (Box 41)
  - Fry, Katherine L, 2006; UA235.002.041.00048 (Box 41)
  - Ghandourah, Ezdehar, 2002; UA235.002.041.00049 (Box 41)
  - Ghassemi, Sara, 2006; UA235.002.041.00050 (Box 41)
  - Gil-Levin, Angelica, 2004; UA235.002.041.00051 (Box 41)
  - Giota, Chrysoula, 2002; UA235.002.041.00052 (Box 41)
  - Griffin, Deborah S, 2006; UA235.002.041.00053 (Box 41)
  - Hopeck, Jonell K, 2005; UA235.002.041.00054 (Box 41)
  - Huang, Michelle, 2006; UA235.002.041.00055 (Box 41)
  - Huber, Kristin Lucas, 2006; UA235.002.041.00056 (Box 41)
  - Islam, Dania, 2000; UA235.002.042.00001 (Box 42)
  - Knasas Irwin, Maryanne, 2006; UA235.002.042.00002 (Box 42)
  - Janicek, Milos R., 2006; UA235.002.042.00003 (Box 42)
  - Joffre, Elexis, 2006; UA235.002.042.00004 (Box 42)
  - Kamalakidis, Savvas, 2005; UA235.002.042.00005 (Box 42)
  - Khedkar, Nina S., 2006; UA235.002.042.00006 (Box 42)
  - Kim, Ji-Youn, 2006; UA235.002.042.00007 (Box 42)
  - Kwak, Hyejin, 2005; UA235.002.042.00008 (Box 42)
  - Le, Hamilton H., 2005; UA235.002.042.00009 (Box 42)
  - Lee, Brian, 2003; UA235.002.042.00010 (Box 42)
  - Li, Xiaojing, 2007; UA235.002.042.00011 (Box 42)
  - Liu, Yi-Wei, 2007; UA235.002.042.00012 (Box 42)
  - Loiseau, Wilner, 2001; UA235.002.042.00013 (Box 42)
  - Loo, Kevin, 2003; UA235.002.042.00014 (Box 42)
  - Marschall, Annika, 2007; UA235.002.042.00015 (Box 42)
  - Mavroudi, Sophia, 2004; UA235.002.042.00016 (Box 42)
  - Mayekar, Sandesh, 2005; UA235.002.042.00017 (Box 42)
  - Naimi, Amir, 2004; UA235.002.042.00018 (Box 42)
  - Nowailaty, Reem, 2006; UA235.002.042.00019 (Box 42)
  - Pantazes, William, 2005; UA235.002.042.00020 (Box 42)
  - Papadopoulou, Styliani, 2004; UA235.002.042.00021 (Box 42)
  - Peters, David, 2005; UA235.002.042.00022 (Box 42)
  - Sabari, Shalev, 2006; UA235.002.042.00023 (Box 42)
  - Sadi, Hanna, 2005; UA235.002.042.00024 (Box 42)
  - Shimizu, Hiroyasu, 2005; UA235.002.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Shoher, Seevan, 2003; UA235.002.042.00026 (Box 42)
  - Sivitz, Julia R., 2005; UA235.002.042.00027 (Box 42)
  - Spencer, Jamison, 2005; UA235.002.042.00028 (Box 42)
  - Stratos, Athanasios, 2005; UA235.002.042.00029 (Box 42)
  - Tekle, Lidia, 2007; UA235.002.042.00030 (Box 42)
  - Thomas, Charles J., 2005; UA235.002.042.00031 (Box 42)
  - Violette, Jean-Guy, 2005; UA235.002.042.00032 (Box 42)
  - Yoh, Seon-Gu, 2003; UA235.002.042.00033 (Box 42)
  - Al-Amoudi, Ibtyhal, 2006; UA235.002.042.00034 (Box 42)
  - Alva, Aurora R., 2007; UA235.002.042.00035 (Box 42)
  - Anderson, Michelle J., 2007; UA235.002.042.00036 (Box 42)
  - Arjomand, Hooman, 2007; UA235.002.042.00037 (Box 42)
  - Basunbul, Abeer, 2006; UA235.002.042.00038 (Box 42)
  - Basunbul, Abeer, 2006; UA235.002.042.00039 (Box 42)
  - Blicher, Brooke, 2007; UA235.002.042.00040 (Box 42)
  - Chen, I-Fang Vyonne, 2007; UA235.002.042.00041 (Box 42)
  - Chiang, Yu-Hsuen J., 2006; UA235.002.042.00042 (Box 42)
  - Choi, Jeong-Yeon, 2007; UA235.002.042.00043 (Box 42)
  - Damanhouri, Wesam, 2009; UA235.002.042.00044 (Box 42)
  - Damanhouri, Wesam, 2009; UA235.002.042.00045 (Box 42)
  - Dhingra (Nanda), Reema, 2007; UA235.002.042.00046 (Box 42)
  - Doshi, Milan J., 2007; UA235.002.042.00047 (Box 42)
  - Fardella, Zaharoula, 2008; UA235.002.042.00048 (Box 42)
  - Farsi, Deema, 2007; UA235.002.042.00049 (Box 42)
  - Farsi, Deema, 2007; UA235.002.042.00050 (Box 42)
  - Ftouli, Maria, 2007; UA235.002.042.00051 (Box 42)
  - Goff, Kristy, 2007; UA235.002.042.00052 (Box 42)
  - Goldberg, Jeffrey A., 2007; UA235.002.042.00053 (Box 42)
  - Goto, Radford Y., 2007; UA235.002.042.00054 (Box 42)
  - Govostes, John, 2006; UA235.002.042.00055 (Box 42)
  - Guidi, Luisa, 2008; UA235.002.042.00056 (Box 42)
  - Hendi, Justin, 2005; UA235.002.043.00001 (Box 43)
  - Htet, Htet, 2006; UA235.002.043.00002 (Box 43)
  - Jaffer, Nurin S, 2007; UA235.002.043.00003 (Box 43)
  - Jun, James, 2007; UA235.002.043.00004 (Box 43)
  - Jun, James C, 2006; UA235.002.043.00005 (Box 43)
  - Kalis, Catherine, 2007; UA235.002.043.00006 (Box 43)
  - Kott, Ian M, 2007; UA235.002.043.00007 (Box 43)
  - Landa, Jorge E, 2007; UA235.002.043.00008 (Box 43)
  - Laskarides, Constantinos, 1999; UA235.002.043.00009 (Box 43)
  - Lobanov, Riina, 2008; UA235.002.043.00010 (Box 43)
  - Lonegan, Christine, 2008; UA235.002.043.00011 (Box 43)
  - Magnifico, Nikki-Jo, 2008; UA235.002.043.00012 (Box 43)
  - Martinez, Hector, 2005; UA235.002.043.00013 (Box 43)